blujay.com 2014-06-29

# blujay help

  | 

Privacy Policy 

blujay believes in protecting your personal information. The following document outlines the privacy policy.

**Information collected**  
Your registration information – In general you can anonymously use blujay's service to browse item postings. In the event you want to list an item, blujay requires you to register. Registration will provide only the necessary information needed for other users to help determine the city your item is located in and contact you to inquire about your item. Your personal information collected by blujay is not shared with any other third party in any other manner whatsoever. 

**How information is used**  
Internal use – The information provided in any part of the service may be used in a statistical manner, however these statistics will not be associated with any personal information or any individual user.   
Disclosure – Only when required by law, or to enforce blujay's Terms of Service, information about a user may be disclosed to law enforcement officers or others.

**Security**  
blujay strives to provide a secure environment in which to buy & sell items, however, no claim or guarantee of security is made.

**Feedback**  
blujay would like to hear from you. If you have any comments on the privacy policy please contact us or leave a comment in the forum.

**Notice**  
The terms of this privacy policy may be amended from time to time. Changes made to the security policy will be noted prominently on the website.

**Google Privacy Notice**  

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on blujay.com. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to blujay.com users based on their visit to the blujay site and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
